Duncan Kinungi

+254704 583 451□ 22713-00400,Nairobi Kenya □ kinungiduncan@gmail.com website: https://danhack.netlify.app/

ICT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Allocation & Maintenance of IT Equipment | Diagnose Hardware and Software Issues | Review and Resolve IT Help-desk Requests

Motivated IT support technician who seeks a new position in dynamic, growth-oriented company focused on cultivating exceptional customer experience and a positive work environment. With experience handling networking concerns, implementing new software, installing new hardware, and addressing user concerns, I bring attention to detail and a dedication to technical improvement to each job. Past achievements include new network architecture component selection and implementation, earning leading industry certifications, and driving the achievement of departmental goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sama-Source Artificial Intelligence Agent

06/2021- Present

API Integration Model Optimization Quality Training AI Data

Silver-Dean Co LTD Call Center Agent

10/2020-05/2021

Building a positive attitude towards customers by satisfying their day today queries.

- Actively working as an Inbound Team.
- Conversant with Ameyo Call Agent App in terms of call Disposition coding.
- Raising Tickets on Atlas and Updating Call Notes.
- Escalating Tickets on Jira.

Quick Call Solutions LTD Team Lead Sales Executive on Safaricom Products. 06/2019-12/2020

Developed and improved the capabilities of sales representative team over the course of one year.

- Received 97% satisfaction rating from customers after completed phone or video call.
- Kept records of customer interactions, processed customer accounts and filed documents.
- Collaborated with team to quickly resolve customer complaints with appropriate action.
- Effectively managed approximately 100 incoming calls daily.

ICT Support Technician

- Troubleshooting system and Network problems and solving hardware/software faults.
- Installation, administration and troubleshooting of various Linux PCs'.
- Setting up new users' accounts and profiles & dealing with password issues.
- Setting up and troubleshooting of multimedia equipment such as projectors, computer system for power point presentations.
- Maintaining the multimedia Bookings calendar up to date.
- Receiving and redirecting calls.

EDUCATION

UNITED STATES UNIVERSITY - AFRICA

Bachelor of Science in Applied Computer Technology - Current

INSTITUTE OF SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES

Diploma in Information Security - November 2018

INSTITUTE OF ADVANCED TECHNOLOGY

Diploma in information communication Technology Management - December 2017

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Mastery of Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) and Google Suite (Docs, Sheets, Slides).
- Comfortable working in both Microsoft Windows 10, Mac OS X and Linux.
- Excellent communication skills with a focus on team-building.
- Outstanding organizational, multitasking, and problem-solving abilities.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

MASABA SERVICES

02/2018-04/2018

Duties and responsibilities:

- Installing, supporting and configuring of WiMAX.
- Pulling cable, Splicing and fiber installation.
- Router configuration and LAN set up.
- Survey of all technologies; Wi-Fi, Microwave, E1.

PARTICIPATION

Linux Administration

Living Open Source an ITGilde initiative (Linux) Hosted at University of Nairobi

REFERENCES

Name: Erickson Kimiti Kibui

Job Title: ICT Officer United States University -Africa

Email: kibserikson@gmail.com

Tel: +254-721-364-251

Name: Samuel Kuiyoni

Job Title: ICT Manager Best Western Plus Meridian Hotel

Email: samuelkuiyoni@gmail.com

Tel: +254-708-919-151